[00:20] Okay, but are you also trying to overlay it exactly?
[00:26] No, not exactly the pop-up comes in the middle of the page but the image, graph image is only towards the left side.
[01:18] So right now the view graph for either the individual one or the combined one, these both all are these are models.
[01:27] So right now I am planning to switch it to a normal window so we can resize it to and move around it.
[01:40] Okay, also you can resize your own graph.
[01:46] The plotted graph.
[01:52] And then you can point your cursor into the line and adjust that also.
[01:57] The points.
[02:15] The real question is, is it actually going to be faster than manual capture?
[02:33] All we have to do is match with the captured graphs.
[02:45] Let us do that is the whole point right.
[02:48] So, instead of clicking now you have to drag the points.
[02:55] Part of times it doesn't align every point correctly.
[03:06] The question is like, you know, when we try to do manual capture, what is the first thing that you do?
[03:16] So what you have done with that is that you have actually overlaid your graph with the previous one.
[03:33] So now you get the exact points out manually.
[03:40] And it possibly takes 2 to 3 minutes per graph.
[03:53] So now if it takes 2 to 3 minutes to drag those points and change it, then that effort is basically wasted.
[04:32] And it can save time on that and then the points is what I am not sure.
[04:38] I mean some points are pretty close but some are not far from the curve.
[04:44] So that we have to manually do.
[04:47] So can we give you like 5-10 graphs that you can try and digitize?
[05:14] So let us give you a data sheet which has possibly some 10, 12 graphs, 10, 15 graphs to digitize.
[05:34] You know, you can try doing some manually and some with AI and see what's the difference.
[05:41] Or you could do the same with AI and same with manual.
[05:54] The second is when you get the data points.
[06:00] Can you, now you are storing it in what format?
[06:05] Those graph data points.
[06:10] So they are getting stored in a JSON format, sir.
[06:14] In JSON format.
[06:17] So if we give you a similar format like JSON.
[06:22] You can map it to that format also, right?
[06:27] So there is a format we received from a customer.
[06:32] It's called dot PC format.
[06:34] And which is almost like JSON.
[06:37] It's like XML like format and they want the data in that format because there is software that recognizes that.
[06:50] And then the second format we can just program export in DC, right?
[06:55] And now it will export that.
[06:57] And then these all of these graphs cumulatively add to the JSON structure.
[07:09] So it's not like there is one JSON for each graph because the data sheet is like the whole data sheet, right?
[07:16] Which we are trying to digitize.
[07:18] So it will have all 20 graphs digitized one after the other.
[07:36] So how about we send you the file and then you start digitizing process.
[07:43] And I want you to do that today on priority.
[08:22] Let's schedule a meeting already for say 9 p.m.
[08:55] All the people and you can send send him right and he needs to digitize so.
[09:04] The customer what they did was they tried to digitize the plot.
[09:11] So they fed it into vision some LLM vision.
[09:16] It extracted the data from that graph.
[09:20] We are seeing that some of the graphs are wrong.
[09:27] So what is happening is that data that they are plotting is actually extracted by LLM.
[09:48] So may then we will send you all the plots that that we have.
[10:43] LLMNG anything from your side.
